

ASHVIN G KANKOTIYA

Web|Graphics Designer

Graphic Designing is my biggest strength and I can do anything and everything related to web/graphics designing. I have 3.5+ years extensive graphic design experience and create visual artworks for various purposes (websites design, advertisements banner, product logos, corporate materials, magazine covers and so on). Currently working on branding, website, brochures and banner designing using Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign and Corel Draw.



PERSONAL INFORMATION

2012 - 2015 MASTER OF COMPUTER APPLICATION Date of Birth: 18th - September - 1989

(GTU-Gujarat Technological University)

Bhagwan Mahavir College of Computer Application-Surat.

EDUCATION

2009 - 2012 **BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION**

(Saurashtra University)

Shree Om College of Computer Science-Rajkot.

61.81%

2008 - 2009 H.S.C.

Shree Dolat Anant Valiya New High School-Bhavnagar.



Gender : Male Nationality : Indian : Hindu Religion

Blood Group : B+ (B - positive)

Marital Status: Married



PROFESSIONAL SKILLS





INDESIGN

PHOTOSHOP



COREL DRAW

ILLUSTRATOR



FIREWORKS



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2016 - PRESENT NV INFOTECH SERIVCES-SURAT (Sr. Web/Graphics Designer)

- Good knowledge of website designing in Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator.
- I am a team player and Working as member of development team and had achieved task related to web designing.
- I have also worked on graphics designing projects like Logo, Branding, Brochure and stationery design.
- Lead projects from creating new designs, schemes to final deliverable.
- Skilled in Suggesting client and make their brand unique.
- · Able to produce the best result in pressure situations.
- · Anything related to graphics design is my strength.

OCEANS TECHNOLOGY-SURAT (Web/Graphics Designer) 2015 - 2016

- Design & revamped over four dozen display panels.
- Produce new idea and concepts and introduce them to client
- Ability to work well in both team environment and individual environment.



DESIGNING CREATIVITY

Branding Logo Design Website Mobile App Stationery Landing Page Brochures Flyer Poster Banner Image Manipulation Mockup Design



WEB TECHNOLOGIES

Wireframing InVision HTML CSS Bootstrap 3



HOBBIES

Cricket Designing Driving Traveling Music



CONTACT DETAILS

Mobile : +91 9016571088

Address: B-104, Shuken Height's,

Singanpore Causeway Road, Katargam, Surat-395004.

Email : kankotiya.ashvin@gmail.com

ashvinwebart@gmail.com

Website: www.ashvinwebart.com



MY EXPERT WORK



Visit: www.ashvinwebart.com